{
    "id": "9b8d5080b9b84e3f9a17fb3b81abe3d2",
    "title": "So, Such, Very, Too",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "It was …………………. hot that we didn’t go out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "such",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5a9d30008e9741e3ab44f272357c5483"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ……………….. old to work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "very",
                "too",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fc2b1b4f28504371af0ab37a5afce48b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The tea was …………………. hot.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "very",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6ee4ad0592d046dabe41a386260ac50b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The milk was …………………. good that we couldn’t stop drinking it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "very",
                "too",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "29434312defb4522880ad631842758ef"
        },
        {
            "question": "It’s ………………… terrible weather.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "so",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "35e5191954bf4f598ab72cb8a7e91095"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is looking ………………….. older.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "so much",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "45854a7fb7f34f4c8778cffc583f84e0"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was ………………….. warm when we were in Vienna.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "very",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cd625fdab2e74929adb4be18998d50f0"
        },
        {
            "question": "He spoke ………………… fast that nobody could understand.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "very",
                "too"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "51032f56946f4687a7ed248268b8c795"
        },
        {
            "question": "Would you be ………………….. kind as to tell me the time?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "very",
                "too"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "77eb102809c84401b59c3c30206546f3"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is a ………………….. intelligent child.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "very",
                "so",
                "too"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a9c9eb4258314a199654590cc6c51936"
        }
    ]
}